# Jagan Mohan Bishoyi

Hard-working achiever, dedicated to on-time delivery, 3 years of experience in developing web applications using various UI technologies. Designed over 30+ websites using bootstrap, WordPress and Magento. Highly skilled in responsive design in lonic, Angular and Bootstrap. Next career goal is to become a full-stack developer.

Hoodi Circle,
Bangalore, 560068
(+91) 890-8348-100
jaganmohanbishoyi@gmail.com
https://jaganbishoyi.github.io/

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **People10 Technosoft Pvt. Ltd.,** Bangalore — Senior Software Engineer

MARCH 2019 - PRESENT

People10 is a web-based service providing company located in Bangalore. There I served as a senior software engineer and my prime work is to design angular UI architecture. As well I was coordinating team members in scrum calls, build and deployment ( Pipelines ), to provide hotfixes, coordinate with clients regarding functionality, maintain codebase, branching and merge strategy and provide solutions and best approaches to enhance application performance.

# **Sulopa Technology Pvt. Ltd.,** Bangalore — *Software Engineer*

APRIL 2019 - MARCH 2019

Sulopa Technology is a web-based service providing company located in Bangalore. There I served as a software engineer and my prime work is to develop and integrate UI with backend.

## **Sulopa Solution**, Bangalore — *Software Engineer*

APRIL 2018 - APRIL 2019

Sulopa Solution is a web-based service providing company located in Bangalore. There I served as a software engineer and my prime work is to design static websites.

## **OPEN SOURCE PROJECT**

I have contributed a package called *ng-password-validator* in NPM. The work of the package to validate input password and check if it is valid or not.

NPM: <a href="https://www.npmjs.com/package/ng-password-validator">https://jaganbishoyi.github.io/ngx-password-validator/</a>
<a href="mailto:bittps://github.com/jaganbishoyi/ngx-password-validator">https://github.com/jaganbishoyi/ngx-password-validator</a>

#### **SKILLS**

Angular 2+ HTML5 SCSS Javascript Typescript Bootstrap 4 Ionic 4 Unit Testing

Git
Bitbucket
Github
WordPress
Web Hosting
Shell Scripting

#### **AWARDS**

In NCAT(National Creativity Aptitude Test ) 2014, I secured all India rank 61 in category 1.

In NCAT(National Creativity Aptitude Test ) 2015, I secured all India rank 61 in category 2.

### **LANGUAGES**

English, Hindi, Odia

### **PROJECTS**

## **Employment Platform(PaaS)**

Generally, this application is about providing employment solutions to Districts/Schools. The school will create jobs and a candidate can apply to a job. He/she can search by zip code for the availability of jobs nearby. And this application has different portals and the super admin can impersonate as another user to the application.

Role: Senior Developer / Core contributor

## Responsibilities:

- Angular architect development.
- Git Branching strategy and code merging
- Developing libraries to use in different projects
- Deployment and Hotfixes
- Training

Technologies used: Angular 9, .Net, IIS

## Menuadda (Restaurant Management System)

It is a Visual Menu for everyone, One stop solution for all restaurants. End to end restaurant management system which helps you manage and Increase the revenue for sure. We designed the admin dashboard using angular 7 and consumer application using Ionic 4.

Role: Team lead UI

### Responsibilities:

- Planning for the development of an application with team
- Development of web applications.
- Converting mockup to HTML
- Designing the UI and binding it with the API

Technologies used: Angular 7, Ionic 4, Node Js, Serverless, Elastic search, Cloudinary image processing etc.

## Periplus(Travel Management System)

Generally, this application is about building itinerary and cost calculation, transport booking, hotel booking, travel agent booking.

Role: Frontend Developer

## Responsibilities:

- Development of web applications.
- Designing the UI and binding it with the API

Technologies used: Angular 5, Node js

## **EDUCATION**

## **GIIT**, Berhampur — *B.Tech(CSE)*

AUGUST 2013 - JULY 2017

I completed my Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science in the year 2017 with 78%.

## Binayak Acharya College, Berhampur — 12th Science

MARCH 2011 - MAY 2013

I completed my intermediate in the year 2013 with 53%.

# RRBP High School, Chikiti — 10th

MAR 2009 - MAY 2010

I completed my matriculation in the year 2010 with 76%.